你居然下厨
You're cooking.
我肯定在做梦  有可能是
This must be a dream or perhaps
噩梦
a nightmare.
我心胸宽广
I choose to take the higher ground
不跟你计较
and ignore that.
早餐好了
Breakfast is served.
这是我专为阿丽克西斯准备的
These are my patented special pancakes
特别煎饼
ahat I make for Alexis.
也没那么特别
Well, not so special.
过去这些年我也学会了怎么做
I learned how to prepare it for her this past year.
学生变成了
so the student becomes...
不及格的学生
the failed student,
辍学生
the dropout.
你给她吃过吗  妈
You fed her this? Mother...
您老人家永远不要
You are forever forbidden
再拿煎饼练手了
from practicing the art of pan-cake-do.
我哪里做错了
Where did I go wrong?
叫我从何说起
Where do I begin?
阿丽克西斯不在家  你怎么要做这个
But Alexis isn't even here. Why are you making these?
你想她了
You miss her.
你不想吗
Well, don't you?
我当然想了
Yes, of course I do.
可是坐计程车就能到哥伦比亚大学
But Columbia's just a cab ride away.
这么多年来她都是我们生活的重心
Oh, she was the center of our lives for so long,
现在她就这样  走了
And now she's just... Gone?
现在是让阿丽克西斯
Right now is just Alexis' time
过自己的生活的时候了
to make her own way in the world.
但她会回来的
But she'll be back.
就像《狮子王》里的辛巴一样
Like Simba in "The Lion King,"
这是生命的循环
it's the circle of life.
亲爱的
Oh, darling.
你对这件事似乎
you seem to have adopted
有了禅的顿悟啊  卡塞尔
a real zen-like attitude about all this, Castle.
我意识到自己偶尔对阿丽克西斯
Well, I realized I've been a little overprotective
有点保护过度
of Alexis at times.
好吧  经常如此
Okay, constantly.
但自从她上哥伦比亚大学后
But since she's left for Columbia,
我学会了放手
I've learned to let go.
我不再去看她的视频博客
I've stopped checking her video blog.
不再要求见她的男朋友
I don't ask to meet her boyfriend anymore.
我开始意识到就像小鸟一样
I've come to realize that, like a bird,
阿丽克西斯需要离巢
Alexis needed to leave the nest.
所以我让她高飞
So I let her fly...
我转过身潇洒地大步离开
I turned around and I strode away.
这叫做接受现实
That's acceptance.
让她高飞  知道她往哪飞
But wouldn't acceptance be letting her go,
并且能够接受  这才叫真的接受吧
seeing where she flies, and then being okay with it?
那我可受不了
Yeah, but I wouldn't be okay with that.
我不想知道她飞到哪里了
I don't want to see where she goes,
外面有些什么样的猛禽
What other birds of prey are out there
其它的鸟巢...
and what other nests are--
你这到底是接受还是拒绝接受
So is that acceptance or denial?
本来接受的
Well, it was acceptance
直到你搬出这套残酷的逻辑
till you started applying your fiendish logic.
不如你们把残酷的逻辑运用到这里吧
How about you guys apply some fiendish logic to this?
这是哈希姆·法鲁克
Meet Hasim Farouk.
昨晚一点被货车撞上
Man versus van at 1:00 a.m. last night.
当场死亡
He was killed instantly.
撞车时鞋子被甩了出去
Knocked right out of his shoes at the point of impact.
撞人逃逸吗
So a hit and run.
这只是冰山一角
Well, that's just the tip of the iceberg.
据目击证人  一个流浪汉说
A witness, homeless guy, said that
被害人一直站在街中央
the victim emptied his gun at the van
对着货车射击
and just stood in the middle of the street shooting
然后被货车撞上
right until it hit him.
他为什么这样做
Why would he do that?
我不知道
I don't know.
但他对用枪很在行  小詹
But he definitely knew his way around guns. Jan.
这是西格P220S手枪
This is a sig p-220-s
上面有重量校正器
with a weight compensator,
瞄准器  定制枪把
target sights, and a custom-molded grip to his hand.
他是非常专业的枪手
This was a serious shooter.
对他还有什么了解
What else do we know about him?
哈希姆·法鲁克是沙特阿拉伯人
Well, Hasim Farouk is a Saudi national
他是在校学生
living here as a student.
专业是什么  都市战争吗
Majoring in what, urban warfare?
哥伦比亚大学  未申报专业
Uh, undeclared, actually, up at columbia.
他在曼哈顿下城区做什么
So what was he doing in lower manhattan?
更重要的是
More importantly...
哥伦比亚大学
what is Columbia doing
怎么会收这种持枪行凶的疯子
admitting gun-toting lunatics
还有这样的人吗
and are there any more of them?
说清楚一下  我不是打给阿丽克西斯
For the record, I'm not calling to check on Alexis.
我只是在收邮件
I'm just checking my e-mail.
接受现实
Acceptance.
叫技术人员查看交通监控带
Have tech search traffic cam footage
找到这辆货车的视频
for any video of that van,
调查哈希姆·法鲁克的背景
and let's look into Hasim Farouk's life.
看看他有没有敌人
See if he had any enemies.
看起来他似乎至少有一个敌人
Well, it looks like he had at least one.
两天前有人起诉他人身攻击
Assault charges were filed against him two days ago
起诉人是布莱姆·斯托克
by one Bram Stoker.
布莱姆·斯托克  《德古拉》的作者  1912年去世
Bram Stoker, author of "Dracula," died in 1912?
如果是他的话  我只能说他是永生的
Uh, if it's him, I'd say he's immortal.
打扰下  布莱姆·斯托克
Excuse me. Bram Stoker?
什么事
Yeah.
我是凯特·贝克特探长  纽约警局
Detective Kate Beckett, NYPD.
请容我说句  你看起来真年轻
And might I say how youthful you look?
真会说俏皮话  没人这样说过
Witty. Never heard that before.
我以前从未听说有人叫布莱姆·斯托克
I've never heard of anyone named Bram Stoker before
除了布莱姆·斯托克本人
except Bram Stoker .
显然  他是我家的远亲
Apparently, he's a distant relative,
我父母都是英国学者
and both my parents are english scholars.
他们觉得起这名字很可爱
They thought it'd be cute.
一点不可爱
It wasn't.
什么事
So what is this about?
已故的哈希姆·法鲁克
The late Hasim Farouk.
已故的
The late?
他死了
He's dead?
是的  在你告他伤人
Yes, he was murdered the day after you filed
之后一天被杀了
an assault charge against him.
肯定不是我杀的
Well, I certainly did not kill him.
我告他是为了保护自己
I filed those charges to protect myself.
为什么
From what?
哈希姆是我的学生
Hasim was a student of mine.
我是一门关于乔依斯的课程的助教
I'm a T.A. for a seminar on Joyce.
你俩之间有什么过节
What was the problem with the two of you?
之前没有
I didn't think that there was one.
直到三天前
And then three days ago,
他课后堵了我
he confronts me after class.
指责我...
Starts accusing me of being...
跟某些女学生混得太熟
overly familiar with some female students.
他说我要继续这样的话
Said if I didn't stop,
就杀了我
he'd kill me.
为了骚扰那些女学生
For harassing those women?
不  我没有骚扰她们
No, I was not harassing them.
我  我也许偶尔
I... I might flirt
会跟女学生调调情
with students on occasion.
但相信我  她们并不讨厌这样
But believe me, it was never unwelcome.
最近妹子们都很迷吸血鬼那套
Ladies are kind of digging on vampires right now.
我又叫布莱姆·斯托克
My name is Bram Stoker.
这名字终于给我带来了桃花运
For once in my life, it's working for me.
也许哈希姆吃醋了
Maybe Hasim was jealous.
那些女学生中  有没有哪个是他女朋友
Were any of those students his girlfriend?
没有  他没有女朋友
No, I-I don't think he had a girlfriend
甚至连朋友都没有
or friends at all, for that matter.
我需要跟你调过情的
Okay, well, I'm gonna need a list of all the girls
所有女学生的名单
that you flirted with.
瞧瞧这栋楼
Look at this building.
作为一个大学生  哈希姆过得可真舒坦
Hasim was living large for a college student.
是啊  这老兄的不思议事件簿里
Yeah, add that to the list of things
又要再添一笔
about this dude that don't add up.
他档案里写着  24岁刚上大学
His records say he started as a freshman at 24.
谁会这么晚上大学啊
Now who does that?
发育得晚吧
A late bloomer.
或者是个潜伏的恐怖分子
Or a sleeper-cell terrorist.
你想啊
Think about it.
沙特阿拉伯人
Saudi national,
手持一支定制枪向货车射击
he shot up a van with a customized SIG.
我就这么一说
I'm just saying...
也许真是恐怖分子
could be a terrorist.
看看他这地方
Look at all this gear.
这家伙有自己的道场啊
This guy practically has his own dojo.
要是他赤手空拳搞不定
And if his black-belt skills didn't get it done,
随时还有这些呢
he always had this.
不止这些
That's not all he's got.
看  还有监控设备
Look. Surveillance gear.
挺先进啊
State of the art.
比警局那些强太多了
Light-years ahead of anything the department has.
是啊
Yeah.
这家伙到底是谁
Who the hell is this guy?
枪支可以说是恐怖分子
Look, the guns could fit with terrorism,
但那些窃听器材呢
but the wiretapping equipment?
也许他是间谍
Maybe he's a spy.
他受过军事训练
He's got military training.
这里写着  他曾是沙特特种部队的突击队员
It says here he was a commando in the Saudi special forces.
还有这个
But then there's this--
每个月都有人从瑞士的银行账户
25 grand wired to him every month
汇两万五给他
from a Swiss bank account.
不管他是干什么的  他资金充沛
Whatever he was doing, he was well funded.
他同学怎么说
What did his fellow students have to say?
我找布莱姆·斯托克名单上的
Well, I talked to most of the girls
大部分女学生谈过
on Bram Stoker's list,
她们都不知道哈希姆也上那课
and none of them noticed Hasim in class
甚至根本不认识他
or even know who he was.
这家伙像是隐形人
It's like the guy was invisible.
他就潜藏在别人眼皮子底下
He was hiding in plain sight.
一名外国特工
A foreign agent
为某项特别侦查任务极尽伪装
in deep cover on some kind of special reconnaissance mission.
那他为什么要向货车开枪
So then why would he shoot up a van?
也许开车的是杰克·鲍尔
Maybe Jack Bauer was driving.
莱恩正在交通监控录像里
Yo. Ryan's hunting through traffic cam footage
找那辆货车
looking for that van.
而哈希姆的事
In the meantime, things with Hasim
愈发奇怪了
just keeping getting weirder.
技术部查过那些监控设备
Tech went over that surveillance gear.
看样子他是在监控
It looks like he was using it to monitor
离他家半英里左右一栋公寓内
an active bug installed in some apartment
已开启的窃听器
about a half a mile from his place.
谁的公寓
Whose apartment was it?
根据租约来看  公寓主人是
According to the lease, it belonged
是这姑娘  莎拉·艾尔玛
to this chick-- Sara El-Masri.
我给她打了电话  还留了言
I called and left a message on her cell phone.
等一下  莎拉·艾尔玛是
Wait a minute. Sara El-Masri was one of the students
乔伊斯课程的学生
in the Joyce class.
她也在布莱姆·斯托克的名单上
She was one of the girls on Bram Stoker's flirt list.
她怎么说哈希姆
What did she say about Hasim?
没找到她  就留了言
I-I couldn't reach her. I just left a message.
伙计们  你们快过来看看
Hey, guys. I got something here you need to see.
不幸的是  犯罪现场附近
Unfortunately, there were no traffic
没有交通或监控摄像头
or security cams near the crime scene.
但我们找到了这段片子
But we did find this footage,
拍下了哈希姆案发那条街的情况
shot down the street from where Hasim was hit.
这辆绝对是撞他的货车
That's definitely the van that took him out.
前后都撞烂了  还能看到弹孔
Front end's all crunched up. You can see the bullet holes.
再看这个
Yeah, now watch this.
等等
Wait. Uh...
倒回她跑出来那里
Go back to where she ran out.
把脸放大
Zoom in on her face.
这是莎拉·艾尔玛
That's Sara El-Masri.
她被绑架了
She was abducted.
哈希姆为了救她被杀了
And Hasim died trying to stop it.
无论是谁  这个人绑架了一个女孩
Whoever this is, he abducted a girl
还杀了我们的被害人
and he killed our victim.
从视频中能看出他什么特征
So what do we know about him from the video?
年近四十的男性
He's a male, late 30s,
无明显伤疤或文身
no distinguishing scars or tattoos.
我们把录像送往了联调局
But we sent the footage over to the FBI
看他们能否用面部识别软件识别出来
to see if they can run it through their facial recognition software.
告诉他们绑架的事了吗
Are they updated on the abduction?
对  他们要派一个探员过来保持联络
Yes, and they're sending over an agent to liaise.
与此同时  我们在检查其他交通摄像头
Meanwhile, we're checking other traffic cams
看看能否找到莎拉企图逃离后
to see if we can track where that van went
卡车的去向
after Sara tried to escape.
哈希姆在监控她的公寓
Hasim was surveilling her apartment
并死在她被绑架地附近
and he was nearby when she was kidnapped.
这是为何  他们是什么关系
But why? What was their relationship?
莎拉的室友要过来
Well, Sara's roommate's coming in.
或许她会有答案
Maybe she has an answer.
他们之间没有通话记录
There were no phone calls between them.
看来更像是他在跟踪她
It's looking more like he was stalking her.
他不仅在她家安了窃听器
Not only did he wiretap her place,
还上了两门跟她一起的课
he was also taking two classes that she was in.
或许就像那部《窃听大阴谋》电影
Maybe it's like "The Conversation."
不好意思  我没
I'm sorry. I don't--
弗朗西斯·福特·科波拉导演
Francis ford coppola.
-吉恩·哈克曼主演  被低估的佳片  -谢谢
- Gene hackm. Very underrated. - Thank you.
在电影里  一个窃听专家
Um, in it, a surveillance expert
偶然听到一件针对被他监听的女人的阴谋
overhears a plot against the woman he's bugging.
或许哈希姆听到绑架的风声
Maybe Hasim got wind of the kidnapping,
企图阻止  却付出了生命的代价
tried to thwart it, and paid with his life.
那也无法解释他公寓中那些枪支
Ah, that still doesn't explain the guns in his apartment.
的确  吉恩·哈克曼可没有军火库
True. Gene Hackman did not possess an arsenal.
有可能哈希姆也参与了绑架
So it could be that Hasim was in on the kidnapping
但中途出了差错
and it went sideways.
或是他临阵退缩了
Or he got cold feet.
好  彻查他的电子邮件和通话记录
All right, dig into his e-mails and phone records.
看看他在和谁联系
Let's see who he was in touch with.
这就去
On it.
我查到莎拉·艾尔玛以下资料
So here's what I've dug up on Sara El-Masri.
她是大二学生  主修海洋生物学
She's a sophomore majoring in marine biology.
生于开罗  家中有亿万家产
She was born in Cairo to an uber-wealthy Egyptian family.
所以有可能是以赎金为目的的绑架
So this could've been a kidnapping for ransom.
她的父母呢
Where are her parents?
艾尔玛家在达科塔有处住宅
The El-Masris have a place at the Dakota.
他们正在赶来
They're on their way in now.
我难过得要死
I am sick in my heart.
我只
I-I just...
我只希望女儿平安归来
I just want my daughter back.
我们正在竭尽所能
And we're doing everything that we can
找到您的女儿  艾尔玛先生
to make that happen, Mr. El-Masri,
联调局也介入了
along with the FBI.
她才20岁
She's only 20 years old,
还是个孩子
a child.
是谁绑架了她
Who did this to her?
目前就我们了解
Well, so far we know that
至少有两人与其有关
at least two people were involved.
司机和这个男人
The driver and this man.
你们认识他吗
Does he look familiar to you?
我不认识  莉娜你呢
No, not to me. Lina?
不
No.
我会交赎金的
I will pay them.
不管他们要多少都给
I will pay whatever they ask.
如果他们要的不是钱呢
What if that isn't what they want?
你树敌无数  安瓦尔
You've made enemies, Anwar.
那是在埃及  不是这里  这就是为了钱
In egypt, not here. This is about money.
绑架案总是为了要钱
It is--it's always about money.
还跟这个男人有关
It's also about this man.
哈希姆·法鲁克  你见过他吗
Hasim Farouk-- have you ever seen him?
见过  我闻讯后曾尝试与他联络
Yeah, I tried to reach hasim when I learned of this.
或许他能帮助我们
Perhaps he can help us I--
等等  你认识他
Wait. You know him?
莎拉不愿带保镖
Sara would not accept a bodyguard,
所以我雇了哈希姆悄悄保护她
so I hired Hasim to watch over her discreetly.
他在哪
Where is he?
他为保护她而死
He died trying to protect her.
你雇了他保护莎拉
Now you hired him to guard Sara.
她有受到过威胁吗
Was she receiving threats?
没有
No.
但是我这地位的男人难免...
But a man in my... position...
我求过莎拉谨慎行事
I-I begged Sara to be careful,
但是她说"爸爸  你操心太过了"
but she said, "Papa, you-- you worry too much."
她现在像美国人一样思考  一样轻信
She thinks like an American now. Tr-trusts like an American.
我愿付出一切
I will pay anything.
她是我的独女
She's my only child.
求求你们
Please.
失陪
Would you excuse us for a moment?
贝克特探长
Detective Beckett,
卡塞尔先生
Mr. Castle,
这位是哈里斯探员
this is Agent Harris.
他将负责这起绑架案
He'll be running point on the kidnapping.
幸会
Good to meet you.
莱恩警探跟我汇报了进展
Detective Ryan brought me up to speed on things.
艾尔玛夫妇状态如何
How are the El-Masris?
饱受惊吓  心痛欲绝
Scared. Devastated.
这是好事
Okay, that's good.
是吗
It is?
比愤怒或是戒备好
It beats angry or defensive.
他们愿意诚实回答并提供帮助  这很重要
They want to be helpful and honest, which is important,
因为归根结底
'cause at the end of the day,
我们信息来源的准确度
it's the accuracy of our information
是决定案件是否告破的关键
that can determine whether this ends well or badly.
有事随时联系
I'll keep you in the loop.
我们也是
We'll do the same.
我派了莱恩和埃斯波西托去调查
So I got Ryan and Esposito looking into
莎拉昨晚之后的行踪
Sara's movements from last night.
我想能查明
I figure if we can find out
她去曼哈顿下区干什么
what she was doing in lower Manhattan,
可以帮助我们找到撞死哈希姆的人
that could lead us to whoever killed Hasim.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我只是
Oh, yeah. I just...
无法想象他们此刻的感受
can't imagine what they're going through right now.
你觉得这真是为钱吗
Do you think that this is really about money?
我在网上搜了艾尔玛
Did a web search on El-Masri.
身价超过三亿美元
He's worth over $300 million.
但是谁会雇佣前突击队员
Yeah, but still, who hires an ex-commando
监护自己女儿呢
to babysit their daughter?
我也考虑这么做
I've considered it.
我毫不怀疑
And I don't doubt that,
但你注意到她妈妈提起敌人的时候
but did you see how he shut her down
他打断了她吗
when she brought up enemies?
他只是不想考虑那个最坏的可能
He just doesn't want to believe the worst,
老实说  我不怪他
and frankly, I can't blame him.
我刚刚见过莎拉的室友安玻
Hey. So I just interviewed Sara's roommate Amber.
她对哈希姆和绑架的事一无所知
She wasn't any help with Hasim or the kidnapping,
不过她说莎拉昨晚出去了
but she did say that Sara went out last night.
去哪里了
Where did she go?
安玻只记得是
All Amber could remember
是什么科学活动
is that it was some kind of science thing.
我找到三个昨晚在曼哈顿下区
Okay, I found three science-related events
举行的有关科学的活动
in lower Manhattan from last night.
离哈希姆遇害八街区远的地方
First, a sci-fi movie marathon
有个艺术剧院举办的科幻电影马拉松
at an art house theater eight blocks from where Hasim got clocked.
不过严格讲  科幻电影是不科学的
Though, by definition, science fiction is not science.
里面有那个词
It has the word in it.
说得好
It's-- that's an excellent point.
另外两个呢
What are the other two?
一个天文学家举办的观星之旅
Uh, a stargazing tour led by an actual astronomer
和一个叫海登·波斯纳的科学家的演讲
and a speech from a scientist named Hayden Posner,
在波蒙特酒店的宴会厅
Uh, in the ballroom of the Beaumont Hotel.
波斯纳博士  他是研究气候变化的专家
Dr. Posner--he's an expert on climate change.
阿丽克西斯给我买过他的书  不过我还没看
Alexis bought me his book, which I still haven't read.
波蒙特酒店也解释了
And the Beaumont Hotel would explain
为什么莎拉会去曼哈顿下区
why Sara was in lower Manhattan.
她是海洋生物学专业的
And she's a marine biology major,
意味着她会对气候变化有兴趣
which means she would be interested in climate change.
走吧
Let's go.
我记得她
Yes, I remember her.
一位漂亮的年轻女孩
A very lovely young woman.
莎拉·艾尔玛  对  她的确参加了
Sara El-Masri. Yes, she definitely attended.
是我为她登记的
I checked her in myself.
你注意到她有不对劲的地方吗
Did you notice anything unusual about her?
没有
No.
波斯纳博士演讲结束后
After Dr. Posner's presentation,
她留下参加了问答环节
she stayed for the Q&A,
很晚才结束  然后她就走了
Which went rather late, and then she left.
知道她去哪儿了吗
Any idea where she went?
我只知道她离开了宴会厅
All I know is that she exited the ballroom.
我留下来做婚宴的准备了
I stayed on to set up for a wedding reception.
她有和别人交流吗
Did she speak with anyone?
只有和她一起来的人
Just the person she was with.
是谁
Who was that?
一个年轻女孩
A young woman.
她们坐在一起  看起来是朋友
They sat together. They seemed to be friends.
但是我不知道她的名字
But I couldn't tell you her name.
可以描述一下吗
Do you think you could describe this woman?
红头发  白皮肤  也很漂亮
Red hair, uh, pale skin, uh, also very lovely.
我能看一下吗
Can I... see that for a moment?
是阿丽克西斯  她也在
It's Alexis. She's on the list.
她昨晚也在这儿
She was here last night.
也许她们认识呢
Well, maybe she knows her.
也许昨晚在活动认识的
Maybe they met at the event.
最起码  我知道她能帮我们
At the very least, I'm sure she can help us out.
这是她的铃声
That's her ringtone.
这是什么
What's that?
我们的失物招领处
Our lost and found.
实际上是昨晚有位客人交过来的
In fact, a guest turned in a phone last night.
在门前街上发现的
They found it in the street out front.
他们把阿丽克西斯也绑走了
They took Alexis, too.
卡塞尔先生
Mr. Castle,
我们会竭尽所能
We will do everything in our power
找回你的女儿的
to get your daughter back.
别这么应付我
I don't want to be handled.
告诉我进展如何
Just let me know where things stand.
从我们掌握的事实开始吧
Let's start with the facts as we now understand them.
你女儿和莎拉·艾尔玛一起参加了
Your daughter attended last night's event
昨晚的活动
with Sara El-Masri.
她们在环境科学课上认识
Apparently they met in an environmental science class
成为了朋友
and became friends.
定位系统显示昨晚活动结束后不久
GPS on her phone shows that it was left outside the hotel
她的手机就被扔在了酒店外
shortly after the event ended.
加上自此以后16小时内
That plus the fact that no one has seen
没人见过她或联系到她
or heard from her in the 16 hours since
我们可以断定她也被绑架了
leads us to conclude that she, too, was forced into the van.
如果莎拉是目标的话
Now why would they take Alexis
为什么也绑走阿丽克西斯呢
if Sara was the target?
她可能当时和莎拉在一起
She was probably with Sara at the time.
目击了一切
She was a witness.
把她一起带走
It would've been easier to take her
比...不带走要好
than... not.
你的意思是
So you're saying she was
她只是在错的时间出现在错的地方
just in the wrong place at the wrong time.
看起来是这样的
It appears that way.
有嫌疑人了吗
Do you have any suspects?
有了名字
We have a name.
面部识别系统查出了
Facial recognition gave us an I.D.
录像里那个男人的身份
on the man in the video.
罗杰·汉森
Roger Henson.
他是个中级毒品走私贩
We know him mainly as a mid-level narcotics smuggler.
知道他是谁
If we know he's out there,
我们就能抓到他
we can get him.
我们可以开始搜捕
We can initiate a manhunt.
我们已经开始寻找汉森了
We're already searching for Henson
以及他已知的全部同伙
along with all his known associates.
但他是个职业重犯
But he is a career felon.
要找到他很难
Finding him won't be easy.
一个毒品走私贩为什么会卷入绑架案呢
What's a drug smuggler doing involved in a kidnapping?
我们尚不确定
We're not sure.
但罗杰·汉森并不是发号施令的老大
But Roger Henson is not a shot caller.
他是个中间人  供人雇佣
He's a middleman, a hired gun.
或许有人雇佣他绑架那些女孩
He may have been hired to abduct the girls.
我们现在要怎么做
What happens now?
我们现在集合各方力量重点追捕汉森
We press ahead on multiple fronts with a focus on Henson.
找到他就可以破案
Locating him could crack the case.
我们也制定了一些临时计划
We're also creating contingency plans
以防绑匪突然主动联系
for when and if the kidnappers make contact.
以防  什么意思
If? What do you mean if?
我们知道艾尔玛很富有
We know that the El-Masris are wealthy,
你也告诉我们莎拉才是目标
and you told us Sara was the target.
艾尔玛先生承认
Mr. El-masri admitted he had close ties
他和埃及前任政要关系密切
with the previous regime in Egypt.
换来的是一些相当有权势的人成了他的敌人
As a result, he made some very powerful enemies.
他女儿被绑架很可能是针对他的报复行为
It's possible his daughter's abduction was motivated by revenge.
那我女儿会怎样
Okay, where does that leave my daughter?
我是说  如果...
I mean, if...
如果他们想绑的不是她
If she wasn't the one they were after
她只是个多余的...
and she's just in the way--
卡塞尔先生  你得积极一点
Mr. Castle, you need to stay positive.
不管他们的动机是什么
Whatever their motives,
绑匪都会意识到她是有价值的
the kidnappers will realize she has value.
我们接下来要做的  就是去你家
Now what we need to do next is go to your home
设圈套并追踪你家的电话
and set up a trap and trace on your phone lines
准备好  等他们来电
so we're ready for their call.
我在外面等你
I'll wait for you outside.
盖茨会看到的
Gates will see.
我不在乎
I don't care.
我真不敢相信竟然发生这样的事
I can't believe this is happening.
我们会找到她的  卡塞尔
We're gonna find her, Castle.
我们一定会的
We will.
你尽你所能
You do whatever you need to do
帮他救回宝贝女儿
to get him back his little girl.
需要什么尽管开口  探长
Anything you need, Detective.
谢谢你  长官
Thank you, sir.
他怎么样了
How's he doing?
那可是阿丽克西斯  他一定崩溃了
It's Alexis. He's gotta be wrecked.
我都崩溃了
Hell, I'm wrecked.
是啊  我们必须把个人情绪放到一边
Yeah, well, we gotta put all of that aside
帮助他找回女儿
and help him find her.
货车查得怎么样了
Where are we on the van?
我们一直在查看交通摄像头拍摄的录像
We've been working the traffic cam footage
有了进展
and we made some headway.
货车离开曼哈顿下城区以后
After the van left lower Manhattan,
我们在东河快车道上发现了它
we picked it up on East River Drive,
驶向皇后区的城中隧道
heading towards the queens midtown tunnel.
我们必须查清那辆车的去向
We gotta figure out where that van went.
我们再找些人手来查看监控录像
Let's bring in some more bodies to review the footage.
找到那辆货车  就能找到阿丽克西斯
We find the van, we'll find Alexis.
你如果需要什么  就告诉我们
You'll let us know if you need anything?
当然  先生
Certainly, sir.
妈...
Oh, mother...
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我真的很抱歉
I am so sorry.
理查德  这不是你的错
Richard, this is not your fault.
我不知道  如果我...
I don't know. Maybe if I'd just--
没有如果  别拿如果来折磨自己
No ifs. Do not torture yourself with ifs.
唯一该怪罪的就是抓走她的那些人
The only people to blame for this are the ones who took her.
阿丽克西斯遗传了她父亲的品质
Alexis is her father's daughter.
她很坚强  很聪明
She is strong and she is smart
她一定会挺过这一关的
and she is going to get through this.
是啊  我知道
Yeah, I know.
不不不  我不是随便说说
No, no, no. I'm not just saying this.
她一定会平安无事的
She's gonna be all right.
我的心能感觉到  我的心是从来不会错的
I feel it in my heart, and my heart is never wrong.
那你的第一次婚姻呢
What about your first marriage?
第二次呢
And your second?
好吧  行了行了
Okay, fine, fine.
有时候  我的心也会失误
Occasionally, my heart is wrong.
但在这件事上不会
But it is not in this case.
我一直在想
I just keep wondering,
那些绑匪是怎么知道
how did the kidnappers know
莎拉会出现在波蒙特宾馆的呢
Sara was gonna be at the Beaumont hotel?
有凯特·贝克特
You have Kate Beckett
和联调局的人寻找阿丽克西斯
and the FBI tracking Alexis down.
让他们好好做自己的工作
Just let them do their job.
他们需要你守在这儿
And they need for you to be here.
好的
Okay.
你们查到什么了
What do you got?
货车出了皇后区  进了城中隧道
Our van exited the Queens to midtown tunnel...
到达绿点
to Greenpoint.
上了绿点大道  到达麦吉尼斯
Took Greenpoint Ave. To McGuinness...
他们向西上了休伦大街
Then went west on Huron.
然后货车去哪儿了
Then where'd the van go?
还不确定  但基本就是这块区域
Well, we're not sure, but this area right here,
由绿点  麦吉尼斯和弗兰克林大道围成的
It's pretty much boxed in by Greenpoint ave, McGuinness and Franklin.
我们调取了那些街道上的监控录像
We check the video feeds from those streets.
货车驶入了那片街区
The van went into that neighborhood,
但再也没出来
but never came out.
两个女孩一定是在那片区域
The girls have to be somewhere in there...
汉森也是
along with Henson.
要搜索的区域有多大
Okay, so how big is our search zone?
20个街区
20 square blocks.
和联调局以及皇后区的警察合作
Okay, coordinate with the feds and Queens P.D.
我们需要逐条街搜索那辆货车
We need to do a street by street search for that van.
只能穿便衣  不能开警车
Plainclothes and unmarked cars only.
我今早坐在南院喷泉边
So I'm sitting by the fountain on the south quad this morning,
啜饮着黑糖玛奇朵
sipping my macchiato,
想复习化学考试时
trying to study for a chem quiz,
我心想
and I had this...
我想这是又一次"新生时刻"
I guess it was another freshman moment.
我肯定最终我会变得厌倦  愤世嫉俗
I'm sure eventually I'll become jaded and cynical,
可今天还没有
but not today.
今天我环顾四周  看到漂亮的楼群
Today I look around, and I see beautiful buildings,
我看到学生们和我一样
I see students who are just like me
却没有共同之处  我感到...
and nothing like me, and I feel...
不知所措  各种各样的可能性中
overwhelmed... with all the possibilities,
我如此幸运  成为了其中一份子
with how lucky I am to be a part of this
这一刻  我是有多不情愿置身别处
and... how there's nowhere on earth I'd rather be right now.
现在准备拉响极客警报
Now stand by for a geek alert.
我和我朋友莎拉
Me and my friend Sara
有今晚去波蒙特看波斯纳教授
got tickets to go see Dr. Posner speak
演讲的票
at the Beaumont tonight.
你们有些人还不知道吧
And for those of you who don't know,
波斯纳教授是气候变化研究的专家
Dr. Posner is one of the foremost thinkers on climate change,
我的心中偶像
a personal hero of mine,
-我等不及要听...  -看到吗  你在看吗
- and I can't wait to hear... - You see? Are you watching?
-他的演讲了  -卡塞尔
- what he has to say. - Castle,
如果绑匪知道阿丽克西斯和莎拉是朋友
if the kidnappers knew that Alexis and Sara were friends--
他们知道  他们一定知道
They did know. They had to know.
他们通过这段视频追踪莎拉到了宾馆
They tracked Sara to the hotel from this video.
阿丽克西斯昨天下午2点36分上传的视频
Alexis posted it yesterday afternoon at 2:36.
绑匪一定登陆了她的网站
The kidnappers must have accessed her web site.
好  我这就联系技术部
Okay, I'm contacting tech right now.
让他们追踪下午2点36分之后
Have them trace every IP address
登陆那个网站的每个IP地址
that accessed that site 2:36 p.m.
这可能需要时间  得看...
Which might take time, depending on--
如果她没时间了呢
What if she doesn't have time?
卡塞尔  听我说
Castle, listen to me--
别
Don't.
除非你能找到她  不然别给我打包票
Don't promise me you'll find her unless you can do it,
因为
because...
我永远也不会原谅你
I would never forgive you.
我更不会原谅我自己
Anymore than I'd ever forgive myself.
有发现
We got something.
什么发现  贝克特
What's that? Beckett?
怎么了
What's going on?
卡塞尔  我得走了
Castle, I gotta go.
我一有发现就联系你  好吗
I'll call you as soon as I find something, okay?
贝克特  等等
Beckett, wait.
好  谢了
Okay, thanks.
好  我会的
Yeah, I will.
刚刚跟分局警督通了电话
That was L.T. from the precinct.
他说他只知道
He said all he knows is that
他们发现货车从昨晚一直停到现在
they found the van parked since last night.
贝克特一有消息就会联系你
Well, Beckett will call you as soon as she has some news.
货车在绿点
The van's in Greenpoint.
她在一小时前就应该到了
She would've gotten there over an hour ago.
她还没联系我的唯一原因是...
The only reason she wouldn't have called--
别说了  理查德
Stop it, Richard.
别往坏处想
We--we don't know that.
亲爱的  去绿点  快去
Oh, darling, go to Greenpoint. Go.
快去  这里我来打理
Go. I can handle things here.
卡塞尔  你来干什么
Castle, what are you doing here?
分局的人告诉我你们发现了那辆货车
The precinct told me that you found the van.
你为什么不联系我
Why the hell wouldn't you call me?
因为我们还没确定
'cause we don't know what this is yet.
卡塞尔  拜托  你没必要看这个  好吗
Castle, please, you don't need to see this, okay?
-车里是什么  -卡塞尔  拜托别...
- What's in the van? - Castle, just please--
车里是什么
What's in the van?!
蕾妮  这是谁的血
Oh, Lanie. Whose blood is that?
有人死在里面吗
Did someone die in there?
蕾妮  她死在车里了吗
Lanie, did she die in there?
卡塞尔  我们还不确定  好吗
Castle, we don't know, okay?
还没查明  蕾妮才赶到
Not yet. Lanie just got here.
阿丽克西斯是什么血型
What is Alexis' blood type?
A型阳性
A-positive.
好  马上就好
Okay, just give me a minute.
快  到这边来
Come on. Let's go over here.
血型匹配吗
Is it a match?
这是B型阴性  不是你女儿的血
It's B-negative. It's not from your baby.
天呐  谢谢
Oh, god. Thank you.
我马上回来  亲爱的
I'm right there with you, honey.
我得去告诉哈里斯探员
I gotta go let Agent Harris know.
那她安全了  她就在这里某个地方  对吗
So she's safe. She's here somewhere, right?
她肯定就在附近
She's gotta be around here somewhere?
现在不在了
She was.
卡塞尔  从车上留下的血迹
Castle, there was a blood trail
一路下来中断了
that led from the van, and it stopped.
我们认为绑匪换了车
We think that the kidnappers changed cars.
谁的车
Whose van is it?
一周前就失窃了
It was stolen a week ago.
有指纹吗
Any fingerprints?
鉴证组在找
C.S.U. is looking.
警员们已经在排查这片区域了
We've got uniforms canvassing the area.
卡塞尔  听着  如果有线索
Castle, listen, if there is a lead,
我们会找到的
we are gonna find it.
我去去就回  好吗
I'll be right back. Okay?
艾尔玛夫妇  我得和你们谈谈
Mr. And Mrs. El-Masri, I need to speak to you for a moment.
我们相当肯定
We're absolutely positive.
我们验了两遍血以确保准确性
We tested the blood twice just to be sure.
那血不是莎拉的
The blood, it's not from Sara.
也不是阿丽克西斯的
And not Alexis either.
那就还有希望
Then there's hope.
对
Yeah.
你女儿也牵扯了进来  很遗憾
I-I regret that your daughter was drawn into this.
他们到底被牵扯进了什么事
What is it exactly they've been drawn into?
我要知道就好了
I wish I knew.
莎拉
Sara?
莎拉  你还好吗
Sara, are you okay?
我想是的
I think.
我们在哪儿
Where are we?
我不知道
I don't know.
等等  那场讲座  酒店
Wait. The speech. The hotel.
我们离开了酒店  然后那个人
We left the hotel and then that guy,
他把我们拖进一辆货车
He forced us into a van
我脑子里一片混沌
and... it's all a bit of a blur.
我想我们是被下药了
I think we were drugged.
我们还穿着衣服
We still have our clothes on.
至少这是个好兆头
At least that's a good sign.
都是我的错
This is all my fault.
从我进寄宿学校开始
My parents warned me about this
他们就一直警告我
since they first sent me to boarding school.
他们甚至强迫我听了一场
They even made me sit through a lecture on kidnapping
企业安保负责人关于绑架的讲座
from the head of corporate security.
等等  为什么会有人绑架你
Wait. Why would somebody kidnap you?
我父亲很富有
My father's crazy rich.
好的一面是  他付得起赎金
Well, the good news is, is that he'll pay the ransom.
这就是他绑架我们的目的  对吧
I mean, that's what this must be, right?
是的
Right.
无论如何  我爸爸会找到我们的
Anyway, my dad will find us.
他和警察一起工作
He works with the police.
他肯定正在找我们
I'm sure he's looking for us right now.
那他们会救我们出去的吧
So they'll get us out of here?
我很好奇里面有什么
I wonder what's in there.
好吧  这太诡异了
Okay, this is creepy.
浴衣  毛巾
Clothes, towels?
这至少证明他们想让我们活着
At least this means they want us alive.
对吧
See?
他们要留活口
They're taking care of us.
是哈里斯探员打来的电话
That was Agent Harris.
目击者看到一辆黑色的育空汽车
A witness saw a black Yukon leaving Greenpoint
刚好在货车到达后离开了绿色区域
just after the van arrived.
绑架者一定换乘了那辆育空
The kidnappers must have switched over to the Yukon.
他们领先我们整整一天
They've had a 24-hour head start.
他们现在可能在任何地方
They could be anywhere by now.
血液调查鉴证组有消息吗
Where's C.S.U. on the blood?
根据血液飞溅分析  血是司机的
Spatter analysis shows that it came from the driver.
他被哈希姆击中了
He was shot by Hasim.
他可能在货车里留下了指纹
He would've left prints in the van.
他的指纹一定在指纹库里
He must be in the system.
不  犯罪现场组只找到了罗杰·汉森的指纹
No. C.S.U. only found Roger Henson's prints.
没有其他匹配者
There's no other matches.
这其中一定有线索
We must have a lead here somewhere.
可能是这个
Maybe we do.
鉴证组调查了那辆货车
C.S.U. inspected the van.
发现车被改装过
Found that a bunch of performance tweaks were done to it--
汽油罐里加了马力加强剂
Octane booster in the tank,
催化式排气净化器被改装
catalytic converter was bypassed,
电子控制器被重新切割以加大马力
the E.C.U. was re-chipped to boost up the horsepower.
有人改装了车子以方便逃跑
Somebody upgraded it to a getaway car.
不是随便什么人
Not just somebody.
他是专业的
A real pro.
可能是司机
Probably our driver.
找出这个人
Okay, look for a wheelman
他的作案手法是偷车并将其改装
whose M.O. is to steal getaway cars and retune them.
他是B型Rh阴性血
Someone with B-negative blood.
好的
Right.
那个安保负责人
That security guy,
你说他告诉过你关于绑架的事
you said he talked to you about kidnapping.
他具体说了什么
What kind of stuff did he say?
要是没人在找我们怎么办
What if no one's looking for us?
要是根本没人发现我们失踪了怎么办
What if they don't even realize that we're gone?
莎拉  我们想想目前能解决的问题吧
Sara, let's focus on the questions we can answer,
基于我们知道的事情
build on what we know.
我们一无所知  这才是问题所在
We don't know anything. That's the problem.
我们不知道谁绑架了我们
We don't know who took us
我们还要在这儿呆多久  身在何方
Or for how long we'll be here or even where we are.
那我们来推测一下
Okay. Well, let's figure that out.
来想想我们在哪儿
Let's figure out where we are.
听到了吗
Hear that?
地下是空的  所以我们不在地下室里
Space under the floor. So we're not in a basement.
这栋建筑年代较久
And this is a much older building,
从破旧的地板可以看出
based on how worn the floor is.
还有声音
And there's the sound.
什么声音
What sound?
没声音
Exactly.
没有汽笛声
No car honks,
没有车辆的噪音
No traffic noise.
要么是这间房间隔音效果好
Either this room is seriously soundproof
要么是我们不在纽约
Or we're not in new york.
被你说中了
Looks like your hunch paid off.
道格拉斯·斯蒂文森
Douglas Stevens.
他在一次银行抢劫案中
He did a nickel as a getaway driver
充当逃跑汽车的司机
for a bank robbery.
猜猜谁是他的同伙
And guess who did time with him.
正是罗杰·汉森
None other than Roger Henson.
监狱记录里有他的血型吗
Do the prison records show his blood type?
B型Rh阴性血
B-negative.
我要发出罪犯的全境通告
Okay, I'm gonna put out an APB.
通知所有医院
And alert all hospitals.
他失了那么多血
With the amount of blood that he lost,
一定需要医疗救助
he's gonna need medical treatment.
他也许用不着去医院
He might not need a hospital.
道格拉斯·斯蒂文森有个做护士的姐姐
Douglas Stevens has a sister who's a nurse.
猜猜今天谁请了病假
Guess who called in sick today.
纽约警察局  开门
NYPD, open up!
什么情况
What is this?
你们要干什么
What are you people doing here?
我们是来找你弟弟的
We're here for your brother.
道格吗  我好几周没见到他了
Doug? I haven't seen him in weeks.
我不知道他在哪儿
I don't know where he is.
是吗  我们可不相信你的鬼话
Yeah, well, we're not gonna take your word for it.
喂  你们不能强闯民居
Hey, you can't just barge in here.
实际上我们可以  女士
Actually, ma'am, we can.
纽约警察局  不许动
NYPD! Don't move.
道格拉斯·斯蒂文森
Douglas Stevens,
你被捕了
you're under arrest.
你把那两个女孩带到哪去了
The girls that you took, where are they?
你的搭档罗杰·汉森在哪
Where's your partner-- Roger Henson?
是谁指使你们的
Who put the two of you up to this?
我什么都不会说
I got nothing to say.
那所有的罪名就都由你来扛
Well, then you're gonna go down for all of it.
货车是你开的
You were driving the van.
一人被谋杀  两人被绑架
That's murder, two counts of kidnapping.
你知道你要蹲多少年牢房吗
Do you know how many years you're gonna be in jail for?
一百年以上
It's in the triple digits.
告诉我们那两个女孩在哪
Tell us where the girls are.
这是你唯一的出路
That's your only hope.
救护车来了告诉我一声
Let me know when my ambulance gets here.
我想跟他单独谈一会
I'd like a minute with him.
我说了我不想谈
I just said I don't want to talk,
所以你无权审问我
so you can't question me.
这是我的权利
I have rights.
律师不在场我什么都不会说
I'm not gonna say anything without a lawyer.
我不是警察
I'm not a cop.
那你是谁
Then who are you?
你还记得那个红头发的女孩吗
You remember the girl with the red hair?
我是她父亲
I'm her father.
你要知道
Please know
我会不惜任何代价把她救回来
I will do whatever it takes to get her back.
外面的警察都是我的朋友
Those police outside are my friends.
也是我女儿的朋友
My daughter's friends, too.
这里只有你和我
So it's just you and me.
你敢动我一下我就起诉你
If you touch me,I'll press charges.
我不在乎
I don't care.
-她们在哪  -我只是个司机
- Where are they? - I'm just a driver.
我什么都不知道
I-I don't know anything.
你知道汉森遗弃了货车换了一辆黑色育空
You know Henson ditched the van for the black Yukon.
他去哪了  他把女孩们带到哪去了
So where did he go? Where did he take the girls?
我不会再问第二遍  他把女孩们带到哪去了
I won't ask you again. Where did he take the girls?
住手
Stop!
斯蒂文森给你的地址是301公路旁的一座农场
The address Stevens gave you is to a farm off route 301.
在警局北面60英里处
That's 60 miles north from here.
哈里斯探员带着一个战术小组
Agent Harris and a tactical team
正赶去那
are heading to the location.
已经去了
Already?
他们现在应该到了
They should be arriving at the farm any moment.
他们会怎么做
And what will they do then?
不惜一切代价救回阿丽克西斯和她的朋友
Whatever's necessary to recover Alexis and her friend.
我一有消息就会通知你
But I'll let you know the moment I have any news.
谢谢
Thank you.
想喝咖啡吗
Do you want a coffee?
不用  谢了  我的肾上腺素就够用了
No, thanks. My adrenaline will suffice.
你查出那个农场是谁的了吗
Did you find out who owns the farm?
没有主人
Nobody.
那个农场从2009年起就被抵押出去了
The property's been tied up in foreclosure since 2009.
一直空着  没人管理
It's been sitting empty. It's isolated.
联调局的人都很厉害
Look, the FBI knows what they're doing.
他们受训如何解救人质
They're trained in hostage rescue.
他们是最有把握营救阿丽克西斯的人
Alexis is in the best possible hands.
我听了州警局的调度室对话
I'm tapped into state police dispatch.
调查局的人现在已经到现场了
The feds are on the scene right now.
那就是我们要找的SUV
That's our SUV.
他们迟早还会再给我们送吃的
Okay, sooner or later someone will show up to bring us more food,
所以我们得做好准备
and we need to be prepared.
安保负责人跟你说什么了
So what did that security guy tell you?
避免跟挟持者有眼神接触
Avoid eye contact with the captor.
那样他们就不会认为你是目击者
So they don't perceive you to be a witness.
很好  还有什么
Good. What else?
装得可怜一些
Be vulnerable.
尽量让劫持者把你当作人来对待
Try to let the captor see you as human,
当作与他们有关的人来对待
as someone they can relate to.
尽量与他们建立信任  建立关系
Try to build up trust, build a relationship.
没有眼神交流又怎么能建立关系呢
How are we supposed to build a relationship without eye contact?
这问题问得好
That's a good question.
她一有消息就会告诉你的
The minute she knows,you'll know.
我想现在就知道
I just wish that minute was now.
这一切发生得太快又太慢
It's all happening too fast and too slow at the same time.
你对道格拉斯·斯蒂文森做了什么
Tell me what happened with Douglas Stevens.
我让他发发慈悲
I appealed to his humanity.
我没想到你还有这一面
I didn't think you had that side to you.
涉及到我爱的人  我就会展现出这一面
When it comes to the people I love, I do.
把下面的食物托盘推出来
Put the food tray under the door.
我叫阿丽克西斯  这是莎拉
My name's Aexis. This is Sara.
把下面的食物托盘推出来
Put the food tray under the door.
这里有点冷
It's kind of cold in here.
能再给我们几条毯子吗
Is there any way we could get some more blankets?
刚才怎么了
What just happened?
对讲机里的那个人说的是阿拉伯语
That man on the radio, he was speaking arabic.
他说  回到各自岗位  有人来了
He said, "Return to your post. We have visitors. "
冲  冲  冲
Go! Go! Go! Go!
联邦调查局  举起手来
FBI! Hands up!
你知道吗  我还仍然记得
You know, I still remember...
阿丽克西斯刚出生的时候  他们把这个
when Alexis was born, they handed me this...
小孩子交给我  她被包裹着
tiny person, all bundled up.
她  一直盯着我看
She just... stared up at me.
当我也看着她时  有种感觉袭来
And when I looked down at her, This feeling hit me...
就像是被闪电击中了一样
Like I'd been struck by lightning.
那就是爱
It was love.
那一瞬间
That instant,
我感到了只会对自己孩子产生的无法解释的爱
inexplicable love you can only feel for your child.
那时我知道
In that moment, I knew.
我的人生永远改变了
I knew my life had changed forever.
而现在我的人生又要改变了
And now it's about to change again.
我是盖茨
Gates.
好的
Okay.
农舍是空的
The farmhouse was empty.
阿丽克西斯和莎拉不在那
Alexis and Sara are not there.
你确定地下室或者密室里都没有她
You're sure she's not in the cellar or some hidden room somewhere?
我们都找遍了  她们不在这
We searched top to bottom. They're gone.
我们倒是发现了这些
We did find these.
有阿丽克西斯的东西吗
Either of 'em belong to Alexis?
是的  那是她的
Yeah, that one there. That's--that's hers.
她的外套在这而人不在这说明了什么
What does it mean that her coat's here and she's not?
这里一定是个中转站
This must have been a way station
他们把女孩们带到别处去了
until they moved the girls someplace else.
他们总是能快我们一步
They've been one step ahead of us this whole time.
我们对付的这帮人非常老练
These people we're dealing with are sophisticated.
外面有摄像头
There are web cams outside.
将我们的行踪暴露给了一个匿名IP
Our approach was streamed to an anonymous IP address.
也正是这个IP上了你女儿的网站
That same IP accessed your daughter's web site.
你们无法追踪吗
And you can't trace it?
踪迹横跨四个洲  很难查到
It was routed across four continents. We're not optimistic.
那罗杰·汉森呢
What about Roger Henson?
他被某个知道他们所作所为的人严刑拷打
He was shot to death after being tortured at length
最后一枪毙命
by someone who knew what they were doing.
他的指甲被拔了
His fingernails were pulled off.
我不明白
I don't understand.
汉森是在为绑架者干活  他们为何拷打他
Henson was working for the kidnappers. Why would they torture him?
我不知道
I don't know.
那你觉得是怎么回事呢
Well,then what do you think?
你猜测呢  这意味着阿丽克西斯会怎样
What is your best guess as to what this means for Alexis,
她们会怎样
for the girls?
这意味着  要把她们找回来可不容易
It means getting them back may be a little more complicated.
你在里面哭吗
Were you crying in there?
我还以为流水声会盖住呢
I thought the running water would cover it up.
莎拉  我们会没事的
We'll be all right,Sara.
我还以为他们只是要钱
I thought this was all about the money.
但这伙人讲阿拉伯语
But these people speak Arabic.
我爸在埃及敌人很多
My father is a hated man back in Egypt.
我们必须逃出去
We need to get out of here.
那扇门是唯一的出路  可是被锁了
The only way out is through that door, and it's locked.
你这是发夹吗
Hey,are those bobby pins?
卡塞尔  我们还是有希望的
There are hopeful signs here,Castle.
他们并没有伤害女孩们
They've gone out of their way not to harm the girls.
他们想留活口
They want them alive.
这会给我们时间来查明幕后黑手
That'll give us time to track down whoever's behind this.
怎么查
How?
我们的首要嫌疑人死了
Our main suspect is dead,
斯蒂文森只知道那农场在哪里  而且
The only thing Stevens knew was where the farmhouse is, and...
我们根本不知道找的是什么人
we have no idea who we're looking for.
联邦调查局已经在搜查农场了
The FBI is searching the farm for evidence.
他们在寻找目击者
They're canvassing the area for witnesses
也许有人看到是谁在农场里
that might have seen whoever was on the property.
这些只不过是说明
All of which is just another way of saying
我们又回到起点了
that we're back to square one.
不会像之前那样了
Won't be the first time.
卡塞尔  我们会解决的  会有出路的
We're gonna solve this, Castle. We will find a way.
"线索更少的情况下我们都办到了"
"We've done it before with less to go on. "
这是谁教我的
You know who told me that?
是我
I did...
我那是盲目乐观
In a fit of irrational optimism.
去看看你妈妈吧  好好休息  明早再回来
Castle, go see your mom. Get some rest. Come back in the morning.
没有人放弃
No one is giving up here.
不行  我不行
No, I-I can't. I'm--
无咖啡因咖啡
Here's a decaf.
路上喝
It's for the road.
谢谢
Thank you.
都试了几小时了
It's been hours now.
我爸教过我这个
My dad taught me how to do this
那时他是为写书做研究
when he was researching for one of his books.
他还弄了一扇门让我们练习
He actually bought a door for us to practice on.
这是最近的事吗
This was recently?
是我十岁时
I was 10.
-老天  -我可以的
- Oh,god. - I can do this.
一根发夹扳着锁孔
One bobby pin is the torsion wrench,
另一根用来撬锁
the other is the lockpick.
我只要小心控制好力度就行
I just need to be careful not to apply too much pressure.
你这是把发夹扳断了吗  那可是最后一根
Did you just break the hairpin? Because that's the last one.
不  我成功了
No. I got it.
谢天谢地
Oh, my god.
外面是什么
What's out there?
走廊  像是栋写字楼
A hallway. Like in an office building.
我没看见有人
I don't see anyone.
万一被抓住了怎么办
What if they catch us,then what?
他们想我们活着  记住这个就好
They want us alive. Just remember that.
这么办  我们穿过走廊  那边一定有出路
Here's the plan-- we head down the hall. There has to be a way out.
如果走廊有两个方向
If it looks like there's two ways,
我们就分头跑  这样总有一个能跑出去
we split up and double our chances that one of us makes it out.
我紧张得想吐了
I think I'm gonna throw up.
你不会吐的
You're not going to throw up.
你会逃出去的
You're going to get out of here.
好  好
Okay. Okay.
-行动  -不行
- Go. - No, no.
我们说好的  行动
We talked about this. Go.
你和别人约了视频聊天吗
Are you expecting someone to skype you?
没有
No.
-阿丽克西斯  -爸爸
- Alexis. - Daddy?
谢天谢地  我想报警  可是打不通
Oh,my god. I tried to call 9-1-1 but it wouldn't go through.
宝贝  你没事吧  你在哪儿
Baby, are--are you okay? Where are you?
我不知道
I don't know.
坏了  这电话要没电了
Oh, no. The phone's about to die.
我们在一栋大楼里
Um, I--we're--we're-- we're in some building.
我们被锁在一个房间里  但逃出来了
We were locked in a room but we got out.
在哪儿  什么大楼  窗外有什么
Where? What building? What's out-- what's outside the window?
什么都没有  我看不见  窗户都被遮住了
Nothing. Nothing. I can't see anything. The windows are covered up.
他们来了  他们发现我们跑了
They're coming. They're coming. They found out we're gone.
宝贝  快跑  快跑出去
Baby, get out of there. Get out of there now.
快  快
Go! Go!
你能追踪到这个电话的地址吗
Can you tell where the call's coming from?
正在追踪
Tracking now.
不可能啊
This can't be right.
怎么了  在哪儿
Why? What is it?
信号是从法国巴黎的信号站传来的
This says that the call originated from a cell tower in paris, France.
救命
Help!